<root>
    <loc1>
        Product
    </loc1>
    <loc2>
        Buy tracker
    </loc2>
    <loc3>
        Contacts
    </loc3>
    <loc4>
        Here is
    </loc4>
    <loc5>
        your time saver~
        tireless guardian~
        easy to use device~
        BloodConnection®
    </loc5>
    <devheader>
        BloodConnection® Blood Analyzer
    </devheader>
    <sidetop>
        This is blood tracking device, which is implanted under user`s skin. Controlled remotely via smartphone and tracking bracer. Sensor is replaced with new one once per 120 days.
    </sidetop>
    <loc6>
        Tracker`s bracelet-assistant helps user to run a rapid examination, spot health problems in time, monitor blood sugar levels and measure the heart rate.
    </loc6>
    <loc7>
        The survey data is sent to the smartphone. User could manage and analyze health status in form of graphs, tables and diagrams then.
    </loc7>
    <loc8>
        The user data is transfered to common database. After this user`s therapists recieve information about their patients` health.
    </loc8>
    <sysheader>
        BloodConnection® Monitoring System
    </sysheader>
    <systext>
        BloodConnection® Monitoring System provides round and clock health analyzing by getting user`s blood composition and measuring the heart rate. Functions such fast blood scanning and listening the heart rate could be controlled with help of rechargeable
        smart-bracelet. It also show system time and battery status. Scanning data is stored in tracker`s memory and transferred to smartphone once it is available for bluetooth connection.
    </systext>
    <orderhead>
        Don`t waste your time! Order BloodConnection® Monitoring System now!
    </orderhead>
    <loc9>
        Region
    </loc9>
    <loc10>
        Phone number
    </loc10>
    <loc11>
        Full name
    </loc11>
    <loc12>
        Email (optionally)
    </loc12>
    <orderer>
        Order
    </orderer>
    <companyheader>
        Introducing BloodConnection® development team
    </companyheader>
    <readergrats>
        Dear visitor, our team thanks you for your attention. We hope that soon you will become one of the multicast users of the BloodConnection® Monitoring System. We also ask you to take an active part in improving our system. The opinion of each visitor is
        important to our team, and especially yours. If you have any questions about the organizational aspects of the program, please contact the contacts listed below:
    </readergrats>
    <graddown>
        BloodConnection® 2017. All rights are registered.
    </graddown>
</root>
